

ABOUT ME

Focused Administrative leader offering 8 years of superior performance in administrative and leadership roles.

Committed to delivering high-quality executive support and coordinating all internal and external operations. Well-versed in managing team performance, coordinating schedules, and implementing process improvements to increase efficiency while interacting professionally with all levels of staff and maintain the highest level of confidentiality; known for tact and diplomacy in handling sensitive issues.



CONTACT

732-374-6271

Kirsten_Kasper@outlook.com
Kendall Park, NJ

SKILLS

- Confidential Document Control
- Insurance Plan Verification
- Letter and Memo Composition
- Reception Oversight
- Multitasking and Prioritization
- · Critical Thinking
- Multi-Line Phone Systems
- · Social Media Management
- Calendar Management
- Executive Management Support
- Office Supplies and Inventory



EDUCATION

Anthem Institute

Licensed Massage Therapist

September 2010 - September 2011

 South Brunswick High School Monmouth Junction, NJ

September 2006- June 2010



Executive Administrative Coordnator

WORK EXPERIENCE

Executive Administrative Coordnator

Pavese- McCormick Agency March 2022-May 2023

- Assists walk-in clients, schedule client appointments, answers multi-line phone calls, and helps clients with questions and issues.
- Supports senior staff with all business documentation.
- Efficiently processes updated client information and payments into a database.
- Prioritizes tasks while staying focused on several projects simultaneously; diligently follows up on outstanding items.
- · Ability to multitask effectively in a fast-paced environment.
- Maintains a friendly, approachable style to help build relationships and work harmoniously with others.
- Manage employee benefits, training and development, compliance, workplace safety, and enforcing payroll policies.
- Gathered, entered, and updated data to maintain HR departmental records and databases.
- Manage Client email blasts along with all Social Media Accounts.
- Managed the CEO and CFO Calendar and travel arrangements, ensuring all meetings and events were scheduled efficiently and effectively while also providing administrative support to executive staff.
- Scheduled and coordinated meetings, appointments, and travel arrangements for managers and crews.
- Contact Insurance agencies to ascertain pertinent information regarding policies and payment benefits.
- Transcribed data to worksheets and entered data into the system to prepare documents and adjust accounts.
- Maintained office supplies inventory by checking stock to determine inventory level; anticipating needed supplies; placing and expediting orders; and verifying receipt of supplies.
- Assisted with onboarding processes for new hires as well as terminations of employees.
- Compiled, organized, and maintained confidential records and reports.

WORK EXPERIANCE

Administrative Coordinator

Office Administrator

Princeton Care Center Feb 2020-Mar 2022

- Demonstrated respect and regard for dignity of patients, families, and fellow employees to promote professional, responsible, and courteous environment.
- Administer and conduct fiscal operations.
- Maintain communications between governing boards medical staff and department heads.
- Report Daily Nursing staff report to State Board.
- Engaged with patient family and friends to provide courteous visit experience.
- Managed supplies and restocked inventory to promote optimal availability for patient care.
- Handled all incoming and outgoing correspondence.
- Gathered, entered, and updated data to maintain departmental records and databases.

Lackernic Chiropratic - Jan 2018-April 2019

- Managed daily operations of the practice.
- Answered all incoming calls on a multi-line phone system.
- Schedule and coordinate patient appointments and physicals.
- · Verify patient benefits and eligibility.
- Vet volunteer students from Drexel & Temple.
- Set up PENDOT Physicals.
- Data Entry along with Scanning all necessary patient paperwork and documents.
- · Collect Co-pays.
- Keep all office supplies stocked and readily available.

Administrative Operations Coordinator

Mark Miller & Associates/ USA BPO Jan 2018-April 2019

- Provided ongoing administrative support to senior executives, driving organizational success through the management of daily operations and special projects.
- Praised for efficient handling of administrative duties. (e.g., answering phones, scheduling appointments, maintaining medical records, processing patients, billing, and bookkeeping).
- Improved the organization of patient files and practice records, instituting new systems that saved time, minimized errors, and accelerated insurance payments.

Sales/CSR Rep

Onyx Enterprises /CarlD.com March 2015-December 2017

- CarlD.com Auto/wheel & tire, rep.
- Onyx is one of the largest marketers and distributors of specialty automotive products sold domestically and internationally.
- Consistently received "Monthly Top Sales Associate" in 2016.
- Continued to exceed sales objectives, outperforming quota throughout two-year tenure.
- Educated customers on product features and technical details to highlight benefits.
- Generated quotes, processed payments, and documented customer communications.